CURRICULAM VITAE

Mujamil G Shaikh

Contact No: +918856905944

Email ID: mujipp786@gmail.com

Address: Flat no 603, The Landmark CHS

Undri, Pune, 411060

OBJECTIVE

I am an adaptable and responsible graduate looking to work in an organization to utilize the organizational skills developed in the past 9 years of work experience. I am an accomplished and fluent communicator with strong investigation and problem-solving skills with knowledge on Customer service. I am passionate, reliable and a motivated individual ready to take up challenges to ensure profitability and sustainability to the business.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

 UPS Logistics Private Limited Administrative Assistant 08 February 2021 – 04 July 2022

Responsibilities:

- Worked as an administrative assistant Back office.
- Created new accounts, made changes in existing accounts and cancelled accounts for shipping.
- Worked for Spain, Portugal and Poland country (Key in entry for all three countries).
- Worked on account summary reports on daily basis.
- Communicated with customers and clients via emails.
 - AffinityX
 Senior Associate
 23 December 2019 05 February 2021

Responsibilities:

- Worked as a Senior Process Associate.
- Worked for order entry and management team.
- Worked on pricing adjustments, promo codes, shipping methods and freight terms.
- Created time tracking sheets.
 - ADP India Pvt. Ltd.
 Senior Associate
 30 October 2016 -13 July 2018

Responsibilities

- Worked as a Senior Payroll Associate.
- Processed Bi-Weekly Payroll.
- Worked on Additional/Out of sequence Payroll, Bonus Payroll, Adjustment Payroll.
- Worked on Service Request Management and pulling Data for the same.
- Doing Daily Audits for Hire, Rehire, Terminated, LOA RFL Employees.

EXL Services.com (I) Pvt. Ltd.
 Associate
 26 February 2013 - 23 March 2015

Responsibilities

- Worked as an Associate.
- Worked for auto and home insurance teams.
- Checked customer's applications, customer's data, updated customer's details and confirm the coverage's as per US states insurance plan.
- Achieved 20 claims target, prepared billing status and number of coverages for every claim by end of the day.
- Communicated with Clients via E-mails.
- WNS Global Services Pvt. Ltd.
 Associate
 05 July 2010 05 November 2012

Responsibilities

- Worked as an Associate.
- Created schedules of flights, checked the available space and amended the flights for cargo bookings.
- Handled customer queries from around the world and booked cargo for individual customers.
- Gave information to customers via email about cargo booking, price and available flights.
- Worked for twelfth-largest cargo airline in the world

EDUCATIONAL SUMMARY

- Bachelor's of Commerce SRTM University Maharashtra in 2007.
- HSC Maharashtra Board in 2004
- SSC Maharashtra Board in 2002.

SKILLS

- Reporting, presentation
- Process improvement, operations, risk assessment
- Customer & public relations
- Customer Service
- Technology aptitude MS Office

Strengths

- Positive attitude towards work
- Fast Learner
- Willingness to take additional responsibilities

Languages Known

• English, Marathi and Hindi